Guide to the National Committee to Reopen the Rosenberg Case Records TAM.174
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II. Correspondence, 1974-2004; 1974-1985; 4.75 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons and 1 card box.
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 17-18)
  - Correspondence, 1983, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 23-24)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1995 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 1991 File (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence and Newspaper Clippings, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1997, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 2001, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - ABC, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - DEF, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - GHI, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - JKLM, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - NOP, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - QRS, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - TUVWXYZ, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - ABC, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - DEF, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - GHI, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - JKL, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - MNO, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - PQR, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - ST, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - UVWXYZ, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Alabama, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Arizona, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Arkansas, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - California, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - California Bay Area, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - California Los Angeles, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Canada, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Colorado, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Connecticut, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Connecticut New Haven, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Cuba, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Delaware, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - District of Columbia, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Europe, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Florida, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Georgia, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Greece, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Hawaii, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Idaho, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Illinois, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Illinois Chicago, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Indiana, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Kentucky, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Louisiana, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Maine, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Maryland, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Massachusetts, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Massachusetts Boston, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Michigan, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Michigan Ann Arbor, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Michigan Detroit, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Minnesota, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Missouri, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Nebraska, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Nevada, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - New Hampshire, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - New Jersey, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - New York City, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - New York State, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - North Carolina, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Ohio, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Oklahoma, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Oregon, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Pennsylvania, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Pennsylvania Philadelphia, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Puerto Rico, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Rhode Island, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - South Carolina, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - South Dakota, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Tennessee, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Texas, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Vermont, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Virginia, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Washington, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Wisconsin, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Speaking Requests, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Speaking Dates, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Speakers Contacts, 1987-1990 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Speaking Engagement, St. Louis, MO, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Speaking Engagement, Lesley College, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Speaking Engagement, Community Church, Boston, MA, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Speaking Engagement, NCJW - Livingston, N.J., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Speaking Engagement, Vassar, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Speaking Tour: Sarasota, Fla., 1975 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Tufts Univ '75, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Speaking Engagement, Press Club, Springfield, Mass., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Speaking Tour, Louisville, Kentucky, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Montgomery College, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Speaking Engagement: Syracuse, NY, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Speaking Engagement: Jewish Center of Bay Shore, 3/21/76, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Speaking Engagement: Temple Emauel, Worcester, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Speaking Engagement: JCC of Greater DC, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Speaking Engagement: Princeton, N.J., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Book Tour, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Book Trip to France, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Film Rental: Ann Arbor Sun, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Film Engagement, Holmdel High School, Holmdel, N.J., 1975 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Militant Forum--Brooklyn Film Showing, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Film Showing: Adelphi University, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Film Rental: Williams College, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Film Rental: Hampden County CLU, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Film Engagement, American University, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Film Showing: Fayetteville, Ark., 1975 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Fund Raiser: Fire Island, NY, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Fund Raising, East Brunswick, New Jersey, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Fund Raiser, Philadelphia, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Fund Raiser: Woods Hole, Mass., 1974 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Fund Raiser: Moss Party = Bklyn., 1975 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Fund Raiser, Brunch: Rose Lewis, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Fund Raiser, Hampshire College, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - AM New York, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Misc. Media, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - The Nation, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Tomorrow Show, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - WNEW: Edward Brown, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - The Churchmen, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - French Broadcasting, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Lou Gordon Show, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Nat Hentoff, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Japan Broadcasting, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Jewish Currents, 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Kennedy & Co., 1974 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - WNEW: Midday, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Liberation News Service, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Mike Douglas Show, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Morning Freiheit, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Newsweek, circa 1975 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Newsweek International, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Panorama, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - "Five Minutes With...", 1974 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Rutgers, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Sample Invitations, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - A. Simon, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - M. Sobell, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Meeropol: Michael & Robby, 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - M. Meeropol, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - R. Meeropol, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous, 1946, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence 1953 A. Katz (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - 1953 - Frankfurter Letter (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Jewish, 1970-1975 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - NCARL (National Committee Against Repressive Legislation), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Ben Goldring, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Mail to Answer, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence from Prisoners, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - "Nuts" File, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Bay Area People, circa 1975 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Perlin, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Letters to Orgs., 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Letters to Congress, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Media Changes Media Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Polish Letter - International, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Permission to Reprint, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Robby and Michael's Handwritten Thank-You Note, circa 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Annotated List of People Who've Written, circa 1975 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Thank You Form Letters to Inquiries for Info, circa 1975 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Thank-You Forms for Money, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Thank You Letters, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Sample Invitations, circa 1975 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Carole Ford - SUNY at New Paltz, NY, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Richard Heath Letters, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Letter to Bella, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Foundations, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Pro Bono Direct Mail, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 70-71)
  - Direct Mail, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - AM. Friends Serv. Comm. (American Friends Service Committee), 1976 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Individual Letters of Support, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Response, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Artists, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Intra-NCRRC & External Correspondence, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - PEN Club, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Peter's Org. Trip Summer '76, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - International, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - German Democratic Republic Thank You Letter, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Congressional Petition, 1976-1990 (Box 5, Folder 82-83)
  - URPE (Economics) List, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - URPE Letter, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Eth. Culture, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Sustainers, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Direct Mail, July In-House Mailing, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Jewish Cultural Center, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Edith Segal, 1978-1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Aaron Katz, 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Center for Workers Education, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Political Rights Defense Fund, 1978-1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Week, 1979, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Sample Letters, 1979-1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Response from Congressmen Letters, 1979-1980, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Aaron Katz, 1979-1991 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Dr. H. Urey (Deceased), 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Prof. Michael Parrish, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Bequests, 1980-1984 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Dr. Lehrman, 1980-1987 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Dr. Nathaniel Lehrman, 1981-1984 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - City Council, 1982-1991 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - New York Times Letters et al, 1982, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Robert E. Goldburg, 1983-1989 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - James Weinstein In These Times, 1983-1987 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Jewish Exponent, 1983-1988 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - John Randolph, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Edith Segal, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Rabbi Emanuel Rackman, 1985-1989 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Bar-Ilan University, Rabbi Emanuel Rackman, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Mike Perlin, 1987, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - B'nai Brith Women, 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Time, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Charles Keller, 1988-1990 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - PauL O'Dwyer, Esq., 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - A. Katz, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Dr. Morrison, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - News USA, Inc, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Association pour le Réexamen de l'Affaire Rosenberg, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Association pour le Réexamen de l'Affaire Rosenberg, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Series III. Promotional Materials, 1944-2005; 1975-1997; 12.5 Linear Feet in 10 record cartons, 1 tall manuscript box, and 1 oversize flat box.
  This series is arranged chronologically, with exception to a large grouping of newspaper clippings that have been organized by topic, and then alphabetically, by the creator. These groupings will be retained. Currently, promotional materials make up the bulk of the collection and are not in any consistent order. If any order exists, it is generally by event or material type (e.g. newspaper clippings).
  This series contains promotional materials such as newsletters, newsletter mock-ups, event flyers and programs, press releases, invitations, bulletins, pamphlets, ads and materials for publicity, transcripts of public appearances, interviews, buttons, posters, photographic prints, photographic negatives, copies of website text, articles, book reviews, notes, speeches, sermons, and drafts for these various materials. Documents supporting this promotional work also include newspaper clippings, research files, and correspondence. Some of the research files in this series include court transcripts, FOIA documents, newspaper clippings, and promotional materials from other organizations. Related to these promotional materials and their research files are works and publications created in response to, or inspired by, the Rosenberg case. Some of these include plays, an opera, music, manuscripts, theses, and books from writers, researchers, and students, and are primarily on paper or as bound materials, but also include audiovisual material such as audiocassette tapes, CDs, vinyl records, and a VHS tape.
  - Pamphlets and Publications, 1944, 1960-1961, 1987, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Brothman-Moskowitz Trial Transcript, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 34-37)
  - Editorials, 1950-1953 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Clemency Appeals, 1952-1956 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Trial Appeals and Court Proceedings I, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Trial Appeals and Court Proceedings II, 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Reactions to Execution, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Committee News Data (CSJRC), 1953 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - National Committee to Secure Justice in the Rosenberg Case, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Transcript of Record, Book 1, circa 1953 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Transcript of Record, Book 1, circa 1953 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Rosenberg-Sobell Newspaper Clippings, 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - On Sobell, 1954-1961 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Rosenberg-Sobell Material and Rosenberg Children's Trust Fund, 1955-1968 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Pamphlets and Publications, 1957, 1960-1961, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Pamphlets and Publications, 1958-1960, 1978, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Old R-S Material, 1959-1960, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Old R. Material, circa 1963 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Committee to Secure Justice for Morton Sobell, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - National Committee to Repeal the McCarran Act, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Cleveland FBI Story, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Biography, Michael and Robert, circa 1974 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - NY Times Ad List, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Speeches, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - To File - Misc., 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Poetry and Articles, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Comm for Defense of Human RIghts in the S.U., 1974 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Guild Dinner for Mike, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Newsletters, Master Copies, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Newsletters and Article Drafts, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Newsletters, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Biblio - Revise, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - N.Y. Times Ad - Text 6-15 & 6-18-75, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Lofton, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - French Newspaper Clippings, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Rosenberg Material, 1975-1985 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Memos: Mar. 10 & 16, 1951 Christian Science Monitor, circa 1975 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Sheehy Memo - 3/10/51, circa 1975 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Memo re Death Penalty 3/16/51 Whearty, circa 1975 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Justice Dept. Memos (2), circa 1975 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Avedon Photo Exhibit, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Morton Sobell, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Ethel Rosenberg - On Strike, circa 1975 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Tapes - Exhibit, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Ads, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Demonstrations, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Cahill-Keene Letters / Legal Theory, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - With Reason and Humanity, by Robert Carl Cohen, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Government Files, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Rosenberg Committee & Bloch, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Sarant - [?] - Sobell, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Greenglass-Statement, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Greenglas statement in re to meeting Rosenberg, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Gold - Sarytchev, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - David Greenglass - Uranium, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Kaufman, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Death Sentence, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Bohr, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Hoover & Golos & World Tourists, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Sobell and Sidrovich, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Hoover & classified info, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - David Greenglass - Ruth & Tessie - uranium, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - David Greenglass - Bernard Greenglass, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Doubtful Yakovlev meeting, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Legal, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Sarant, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Julius Rosenberg Communist Party, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence and Jewish Currents, 1975, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Fact Sheet on FOIA Suit, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - The Crucible, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Workshops - Nat'l Conf., 1975 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Press Releases, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - "Unquiet Death", 1975 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - The Cannons of Judicial Ethics, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Government Files, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - FBI Memo, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Article from Advertiser - Montgomery, Ala 10/30/75, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Dave Gelman (Files) Gelman Article Newsday - 5/25/75, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Washington Star - 11/14/75, Daily News - 11/17/75, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Article in Rights 10/75 "Behind the Death Sentence", 1975 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Washington Post - 12/6/75 "Key Rosenberg Witness Altered Story", 1975 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Jewish Editor Welcomes Reopening of Case -- 8/10/75, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Action Bull. #1, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Political Action Bull. #2, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Political Action Bulletin #3, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Political Action Bulletin #4, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Political Action Bulletin #5, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Political Action Bulletin #6, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Bulletin #7, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Political Action Bulletin #8, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Political Action Bulletin #9, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Political Action Bulletin #10, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - P.A. Bulletin #11, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - P.A. Bulletin #12, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - P.A. Bulletin #12A, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - P.A. Bulletin #13, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - P.A Bulletin #14, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - P.A. Bulletin #15, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Political Actions Bulletins 1-12, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Political Action Bulletins, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Legal File, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Black Press, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - NYT Ad: Sponsors, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Meeropol Request for Files, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Press Release - Dec. 8, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Press Release 12/2/75 FBI-CIA Waive Ransom, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Press Release - 10/12/75 French Book Tour, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Press Release 8/26/75 re: 8/22/75 Court order, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Press Release - 8/19/75 pre-Aug. 22 court hearing (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Press Release 8/4/75 "Judge Green enjoins gov't agencies from further destruction of R-S papers", 1975 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Press Release 7/11/75 "Dept. of Justice refutes Wash. Star story as Inaccurate", 1975 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Press Release 7/9/75 "Rosenberg Sons Sue 7 Govt. Agencies", 1975 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Press Release 6/10/75 On French Film, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Michael's Pamphlet Proposal, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Nov. 22 Mailing, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - S-1 (Criminal Justice Reform Act of 1975), 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Senate Bill #1, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 72-73)
  - Sermons, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Robby's Theory Paper, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Interviews: Emply & Meeropols, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Newsletters, Correspondence, Research Materials, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Press Releases, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Negatives, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Conference Calls and Press Release, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Ethical Culture 6/19/75 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Ballantine, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Spring Action May 1-8, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Kaufman Papers: Introduction UPI Release, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Pamphlets and Publications, 1976, 1983, 1987, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Press Release: July 22 Hearing, Wash., 1976 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Sobell Released from Parole, 6/24/76, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Press Release 5/28/76 Demo. to Open Ros.-Sobell files Carnegie Hall, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Countryman Letter, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - News Release "Disqualify" 10/13/76, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Depositions (FBI) Wash. Sept. 1976 (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Robbie's Response to Tom Tiede, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Press Release 4/20/76 Dems. Historians, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Press Release - 1/20/76 "Rosenberg Sons Welcome New ABA Panel", 1976 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Press Release - Jan. 7, 1976, Pre-Court Appearance (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Kaufman Papers, circa 1976 (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Film, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - The Front, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Originals from Printer, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Forums, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Demo. Party Resolution, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Letters to Editor (& Columnists) by R & M, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - "The Front": Film Reviews, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - "Trial of Julius & Ethel Rosenberg" -- Video Drama, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Carnegie Hall Tribute, June 15, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - "Inquest", 1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Village Gate Benefit 8/24/76, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - French Documentary Film on Rosenbergs, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - National Lampoon Bicentennial Calendar, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - "Jews on Trial" Program - Union of American Hebrew Congregations, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Book Reviews: Book of Daniel, Doctorow, On Doing Time, Sobell, Unquiet Death, Goldstein, Public Burning of Ethel & Julius Rosenberg, Robert Coover, 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - We Are Your Sons Book Reviews, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - "Unquiet Death", 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Saypol Indictment 5/76, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Senator Church's Senate Select Committee on Intelligence - Request for Classified FBI Documents, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Freedom of Information Act - General, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - FBI Memo: Kaufman Papers, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Release of FBI Files: General, December '75, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - FBI Files: Satellite Platform - Greenglass, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - FBI Files: Rosenbergs Seen as Part of Spy Network, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - FBI Files: Greenglass Initially Implicated Only Julius, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - FBI Files: Tartakow's Report - Julius "Played Game, Lost", 1975 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - FBI Files: Death Penalty Story, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - FBI Files: Mario Russo Report - Rosenbergs Expected Light Sentence, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - FBI Files: Tartakow's Report - Rosenbergs Determined to Die Silently, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Kaufman Story & Judge Green Hearing -- Media Pickup, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Nizer Appeal, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Files - New York U.S. Attorney's Office, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - U.S. Attorney's Office Files: Hoover's "Mercy" for Ethel, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 30)